Guide to the Administrative Papers of President John Crittenden Sawhill 1974-1981 (Bulk 1975-1979) RG.3.0.8
New York University Archives
- Series III: Development
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (International Business Machines (IBM)), Oct 1968-Mar 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (International Telephone and Telegraph Company), Feb 1977-Jan 1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Iro-It), Dec 1972-Apr 1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ja), Nov 1973-Nov 1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Je-Jm), Nov 1973-Feb 1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Jo-Ju), Nov 1973-Jun 1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ka), Oct 1976-Feb 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ke), Jan 1969-May 1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ki-Kn), Apr 1973-Dec 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ko-Ku), Jan 1975-Aug 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Kresge Foundation), Mar 1970-Jul 1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (La), Dec 1972-Jun 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Lasdon, William S.), Nov 1969-Oct 1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Lasker, Mrs. Albert [Mary]), Jan 1955-Apr 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Le), Mar 1974-Aug 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Li), Jan 1969-Mar 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Lo-Lu), Dec 1966-Jun 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (M-Man), Dec 1975-Apr 1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Mao-Mar), Feb 1969-Apr 1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Markle Foundation), Jul 1969-May 1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Mas-Mc), Jun 1967-Dec 1979 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Me), May 1968-Aug 1980 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Merrill Trust, Charles E), Jul 1965-Sep 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Mi), Apr 1971-Sep 1979 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Mo), Feb 1969-Mar 1979 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Mobil Oil), Dec 1968-Apr 1979 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Mu), Mar 1971-Jan 1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Na), Jun 1969-Feb 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (National Science Foundation), Feb 1976-/1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ne-News), Jun 1973-Jul 1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (New York), Sep 1969-Apr 1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (New York Foundation), Sep 1972-Dec 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ni-Ny), Jun 1976-Sep 1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (O), Mar 1974-Nov 1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Olin Foundation), Mar 1952-Jun 1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Pa-Pep), Jan 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Per-Ph), Jun 1974-Aug 1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Pi-Pu), May 1976-Feb 1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ra-Rh), Jul 1976-Oct 1980 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (RCA Corporation), Jan 1964-Nov 1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ri), Feb 1969-Sep 1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ro), Aug 1975-Feb 1980 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Rockefeller Family Funds), Nov 1975-Jul 1979 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ru), Aug 1975-Jun 1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Sa), Oct 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Sc), Jul 1971-Nov 1980 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Schimmel, Michael), Oct 1957-Jun 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Schnitzer, Henry R. Foundation), May 1972-Feb 1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Sea-Sey), Jan 1974-Nov 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Sha-Shu), Aug 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Si-Sky), Feb 1970-Nov 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Sl-So), Mar 1976-Feb 1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Sp-Sq), Jul 1972-May 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Sta-Stu), Jan 1976-Nov 1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Su-Sw), May 1973-Oct 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Svigals, Philip), Apr 1961-Oct 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ta-Ten), Oct 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ter-Ti), Jul 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (To-Tz), Jul 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (U), Apr 1975-Nov 1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (V), Jun 1976-Nov 1978 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Wa), Dec 1972-Jul 1980 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (We), Sep 1976-Jan 1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Wh-Wi), Jun 1973-Jul 1980 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Wo-Wy), Aug 1976-Sep 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Xerox), Aug 1975-Jun 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Y-Z), Dec 1975-Jan 1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising, Deans and Directors Views, Aug 1975-Sep 1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising, Deans and Directors Views, Oct 1975-Nov 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising, School Campaigns; Arts and Science, Oct 1976-Oct 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, School Campaigns; Graduate School of Business Administration, Jun 1977-May 1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising, School Campaigns; Dental School, Aug 1975-Feb 1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising, School Campaigns; School of Education, Aug 1978-Jan 1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising, School Campaigns; School of the Arts, Sep 1975-Sep 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising, School Campaigns; Real Estate Institute, Aug 1975-Oct 1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Gallatin Fellows, Sep 1971-Aug 1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Gallatin Fellows, Sep 1978-Aug 1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Gifts and Grants, Mar 1969-Jul 1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Gifts and Pledges, Reports, Aug 1975-Jul 1979 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - New Development Campaign, Jan 1976-Mar 1979 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - New Development Campaign; Medical Center, Apr 1976-Oct 1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - New York University: Our Presence in New York (draft), Apr 1977 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Series IV: Facilities and Services
  This series, a modest .624 linear foot, in 1.5 Hollinger boxes, covers a period of limited construction, facilities upgrading, and an emphasis on energy conservation as cost-saving. Box 24, folders 1-2 offer an inventory of existing academic space. Information on the conception and development of the School of Continuing Education's Midtown Center is found in Box 24, folder 11. Sawhill initiated the purchase of a VIP apartment at 1 Fifth Avenue, Box 25, folder 6.
  Some selected information concerning dormitories, including some press coverage and correspondence about the proposed eviction of several long-term tenants whose occupancy in the Brittany Hotel pre-dated the University's purchase of it for dormitory use, book centers, classroom space and food services are found in Box 24, while some matters pertaining to real estate, insurance, and security are located in Box 25. Individual housing requests have been discarded.
  - Academic Buildings; Survey and Operational Cost Analysis; pp 1-18, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Academic Buildings; Survey and Operational Cost Analysis; pp 19-53, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Book Centers, Sep 1975-Jan 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Classroom Space, Oct 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Energy Conservation, Dec 1975-Dec 1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Energy Conservation, Jan 1980-Aug 1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Food Services, Aug 1975-Mar 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic; Bobst Library, Aug 1975-Jan 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic; Dental Center, Aug 1975-Apr 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic; Institute of Fine Arts (IFA) proposal, Oct 1977-Apr 1978 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic; Midtown Center, Aug 1978-Feb 1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic; Rufus Smith Hall, Dec 1979 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic; Vanderbilt hall, Apr 1975-May 1976 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Institutional Facilities, Dormitories; Brittany Hall, Nov 1973-May 1974 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Institutional Facilities, Dormitories; Judson Hall, Mar 1974-Sep 1978 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Institutional Facilities, Dormitories; Judson Hall; Miscellaneous, Oct 1972-Oct 1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Insurance, Sep 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate; Apartments, Aug 1975-Mar 1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate; Automation House, Jan 1978-Apr 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate; Hebrew Union College, Sep 1976-Nov 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate; Loft Conversion (250 Mercer Street), Jun 1977-Dec 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate; VIP Apartment (1 Fifth Avenue, 15g), Aug 1978-Apr 1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate; Washington Square Village Refinancing, Sep 1975-Jan 1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate; Complaints, Dec 1975-May 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Real Estate; Miscellaneous, Nov 1973-Dec 1976 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Real Estate; Miscellaneous, Jan 1977-Oct 1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Security and Protection, Aug 1975-Jun 1980 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Series V: Finances
  This modest assemblage of material is contained in approximately 2.5 Hollinger boxes, for a total of 1.041 linear feet. The University budget sequence reflects the nature of the efforts made to contain spending and eliminate the deficit. In Box 25, folder 14 Sawhill advises officers and deans of an "unacceptable" deficit forecast, 10/15/75; in folder 15 he announces a "strict freeze on all hiring," 1/9/76 and Dean Dick Netzer defends the budgets of the "poor" schools, such as the Graduate School of Public Administration, 1/21/76.
  Early in Sawhill's tenure, in a major restructuring, he appointed Allan E. Claxton Vice President for Finance, effectively removing from the Chancellor's purview those budgetary responsibilities and fiscal control mechanisms previously under his aegis, Box 39, folder 7, Sawhill to Trustees' Financial Affairs Committee 12/5/75, NYU Press Release 2/4/76. Claxton's involvement can be seen beginning with Box 26, folder 1, 4/2/76, folder 2, 6/30/76. For continuing progress in containing the deficit, see folder 4, Sawhill 1/31/77, folder 5, Sawhill 3/9/78. For some history of the deficit and further detail, see Box 27, folder 1, Borowitz to Trustees, spring '75, Borowitz Papers (RG 6.0.7), Boxes 29 and 30, and Senate Financial Affairs Committee (RG 14).
  - Bonds, Nov 1975-May 1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Budget, Jun 1975-Jul 1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Budget, Aug 1975-Oct 1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Budget, Nov 1975-Jan 1976 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Budget, Feb 1976 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Budget, Mar 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Budget, May 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Budget, Jul 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Budget, Sep 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Budget, Mar 1977-Mar 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Budget, Apr 1978-May 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Budget, Jun 1978-Jul 1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Budget, Aug 1978-Nov 1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Budget, Jan 1979-Aug 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Budget; Advisory Group, Jun 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Budget; Five Year Financial Plan, Sep 1972-Aug 1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Budget Task Force, Aug 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Contract Office, Aug 1975-Mar 1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Controller's Division, Apr 1975-Jul 1978 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Financial Crisis; at NYU; Miscellaneous, Jan 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Financial Crisis; in Higher Education, Jun 1975-Sep 1978 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports; Miscellaneous, Jun 1975-Oct 1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports; NYU External Auditors, Nov 1976-Nov 1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fiscal Review Group, Apr 1975-May 1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Fiscal Review Group, Jun 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Fiscal Review Group, Sep 1975-Mar 1977 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Investments, Dec 1974-May 1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Investments, Jun 1977-Jul 1980 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Investments; First National City Loan Agreement, Jan 1976 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Medical Malpractice Trust Fund, Nov 1977 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Salaries, Nov 1976-May 1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Series VI: Governance
  Within the 7 Hollinger boxes of this series, a total of 2.916 linear feet, are found materials from the primary components by and through which the University operates, namely the Board of Trustees, President's and Officers Groups, and University Senate. Changes in the ways in which university business was conducted, such as the appointment of a Vice President for Finance, noted in Series V, resulted from Sawhill's managerial-mindedness. He placed early emphasis on creating "a more effective" Board of Trustees, Payne to Sawhill 5/27/75 and following, Box 28, folder 1. For the involvement of trustees in the School of Law's planning process arising from that school's improved financial base following the Mueller sale, see Sawhill to the Board of Trustees 12/6/76, Box 28, folder 2 along with the Historical Note and Series X, Schools and Divisions, School of Law section. In folder 2 Sawhill alerts the trustees to new marketing plans 4/6/77. In folder 3 perhaps his interest in trustee involvement had cooled over time, see Taggart Whipple to Sawhill 3/15/78.
  Among the historical materials sprinkled through the Sawhill papers is a 9/74 report to the trustees regarding the status of the Dental Center, hand-edited by James M. Hester, Box 28, folder 7. The trustees' involvement in long range planning is reflected in Box 28, folder 9, Baruch to Sawhill 4/16/79. A long range planning sequence appears in Box 29, folders 14-20 and Box 30, folders 1-3. For budget issues and information presented to the trustees see Sawhill to the Financial Affairs Committee 1/26/78, Box 28, folder 15.
  Sawhill, in reorganizing the Office of the President, created the post of Vice President for Academic Affairs in lieu of Chancellor, thus connecting more closely the oversight and conduct of academic matters with the President. One outcome was Sawhill's assuming from the departing Chancellor the chair of the weekly Deans meeting, Box 30, folder 14, Sawhill to the Vice Presidents 1/7/77 and to the Deans 1/7/77. Other academic matters jointly considered by the President and Deans Council were a 7/29/77 Sawhill memorandum identifying a marketing problem with "serious implications" for the University, Box 31, folder 1, Andrew Schaffer's review of a faculty committee report on financial exigency, Box 31, folder 9, 3/7/79 and Sawhill's prioritization of the humanities; his interim report to the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation 5/78 on the reorganization of NYU's Humanities Council addresses some results of that new focus, Box 32, folder 12.
  The material covering the conduct and business of the University Senate is limited and somewhat routine. It might be surmised that many matters before the Senate were of less interest to the President than to the officers, deans and faculty delegates.
  - Board of Trustees, May 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, May 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees, May 1977-Mar 1978 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees, May 1978-Apr 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, May 1979-Jun 1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees; By-Laws, Nov 1977-Jul 1980 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees, Sep 1974-Jul 1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Academic Affairs, Dec 1976-Mar 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Academic Affairs, Oct 1978-Feb 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Committee on Trustees, Nov 1974-Apr 1976 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Committee on Trustees, Jun 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Executive, Sep 1975-Sep 1980 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Executive (Honors Subcommittee), Feb 1976-Mar 1978 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Financial Affairs, Oct 1975-Aug 1977 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Financial Affairs, Sep 1977-Apr 1978 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Financial Affairs, Sep 1978-Oct 1980 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Special Committee on Administration, May 1980-Aug 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Student Affairs, Nov 1976-Mar 1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Subcommittee on Investments, Oct 1975-Mar 1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Meeting Materials, Oct 1976-May 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Executive Committee, Nov 1976-Apr 1979 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees; Committees; Members: NYU Report, Feb 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Committees; Computing Advisory and Working Committees, Dec 1978-Dec 1979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Committees; Computing Advisory and Working Committees, Jan 1980-Jul 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Committees; Deans Review, Feb 1973-Mar 1978 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Committees; Faculty Development, May 1977-Feb 1979 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Committees; Faculty Self-Governance, Apr 1976-Jun 1978 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Committees; Financial Exigency Procedures, Apr 1976-May 1978 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Committees; Institutional Emergencies, Apr 1976-Dec 1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Sep 1977-Nov 1977 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Dec 1977-Feb 1978 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Apr 1978 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Sep 1978-Nov 1978 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Dec 1978 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Jan 1979 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Feb 1979 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Mar 1979-Apr 1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, May 1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Committees; Long Range Planning, Dec 1979-Jun 1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Committees; Compensation; Miscellaneous, May 1977-Jul 1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Committees; NYU Response to NYC Fiscal Crisis, Apr 1976-Sep 1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Committees; Staff Classification and Compensation Advisory Committee, Apr 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Committees; Task Force on Graduate Student Marketing Research and Plan, Mar 1978 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Committees; Task Force on Intercollegiate Athletics, Oct 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Committees; Task Force to Review Undergraduate Admissions Publications System, Nov 1976-Oct 1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Committees; University Professorship Procedures, Apr 1978-Oct 1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Councils and Commissions; Administrative Management Council, Apr 1975-Mar 1976 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Councils and Commissions; Commission on Academic Planning, Feb 1976-Sep 1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Correspondence, Sep 1975-Oct 1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Dec 1975-Feb 1977 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Mar 1977-May 1977 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Jun 1977-Aug 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Sep 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Jan 1978-Mar 1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Apr 1978-Aug 1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Sep 1978-Oct 1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Nov 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Dec 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Jan 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Feb 1979-Mar 1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Apr 1979-May 1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Jun 1979-Jul 1979 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Aug 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Sep 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meetings, Dec 1979-Mar 1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council: Meeting Minutes, Sep 1975-Dec 1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Councils and Commissions; Deans Council; School Organizational Charts, Jun 1977-Aug 1977 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Councils and Commissions; Faculty Council, Apr 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Councils and Commissions; Faculty Council, Oct 1976-Jun 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Councils and Commissions; Faculty Council, Sep 1977-Aug 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Councils and Commissions; Faculty Council; Meeting Minutes, Sep 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Councils and Commissions; Graduate Commission, Mar 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Councils and Commissions; Graduate Commission, Oct 1977-Apr 1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Councils and Commissions; Humanities Council, Nov 1975-Aug 1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Councils and Commissions; Humanities Council, Sep 1977-Aug 1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Councils and Commissions; Humanities Council, Oct 1978-Jun 1980 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Councils and Commissions; Humanities Council; Ethics Colloquium, Apr 1978-Jan 1980 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Councils and Commissions; Undergraduate Education, Feb 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Councils and Commissions; Undergraduate Education, Nov 1977-Nov 1978 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - President, Deans Annual Reports: Correspondence, Aug 1974-Dec 1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - President's Meetings; Critical Issues Meetings, Feb 1976-May 1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - President's Meetings; Staff Meetings; Action Memoranda, Jun 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - President's Meetings; Tuesday Morning Meetings, Jan 1977-Aug 1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - President's Meetings; Weekly Meetings: Agendas, Feb 1976-Sep 1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - President's Meetings; Weekly Meetings: Minutes, May 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - President's Meetings; Weekly Meetings: Minutes, Sep 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - President's Meetings; Weekly Meetings: Miscellaneous, Jan 1976-Jun 1980 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - President's Meetings; Weekly Meetings and Joint Meetings of Deans and Vice Presidents: Agendas, Jun 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - President's Meetings; Weekly Meetings and Joint Meetings of Deans and Vice Presidents: Agendas and Minutes, Sep 1976-Jan 1977 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - President's Office; Christmas Card Lists, Sep 1978-Nov 1979 (Box 33, Folder 11)